<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>NSX-T - Etiqueta - 288clouds</title>
        <link>https://288clouds.com/es/tags/nsx-t.html</link>
        <description>NSX-T - Etiqueta - 288clouds</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>es</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 05:52:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://288clouds.com/es/tags/nsx-t.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>On-demand NSX-T Networks with vRA Cloud in VMC on AWS VS. On-Prem vSphere</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/es/2021-03-30-vrac-nsxt-on-demand-networks-vmc-on-prem-differences.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 05:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Autor</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/es/2021-03-30-vrac-nsxt-on-demand-networks-vmc-on-prem-differences.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[~ Este post será traducido al español próximamente ~ You can create on-demand NSX-T networks using a vRA Cloud template in a VMC on AWS environment as well as in an on-prem vSphere environment. However, there are some differences between how on-demand NSX-T networks are created in these two environments due to limitations with vRA at the time of writing this post.
On-demand Network Types vRA Cloud Assembly has several on-demand network types available depending on the resource you choose.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Creating On-demand Distributed Firewall Rules in VMC on AWS with vRA Cloud</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/es/2021-03-29-vrac-vmc-nsxt-on-demand-dfw.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 05:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Autor</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/es/2021-03-29-vrac-vmc-nsxt-on-demand-dfw.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[~ Este post será traducido al español próximamente ~ Let&rsquo;s explore how you can create on-demand distributed firewall rules in a VMC on AWS environment with a vRA Cloud template.
Demo Product Versions  vRA Cloud VMC on AWS (SDDC version 1.13)  Prerequisites VMC on AWS:
 Active SDDC  vRA Cloud:
 Basic infrastructure configured for the VMC on AWS environment (Cloud Proxy, Cloud Account, Project, Cloud Zone, Flavor Mapping, Image Mapping)  Process Overview  Create a template that adds a new security group to the deployment.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Using On-demand NSX-T Security Groups in VMC on AWS with vRA Cloud</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/es/2021-03-23-vrac-vmc-nsxt-on-demand-security-groups.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 05:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Autor</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/es/2021-03-23-vrac-vmc-nsxt-on-demand-security-groups.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[~ Este post será traducido al español próximamente ~ There are different ways you can create on-demand NSX-T security groups in a VMC on AWS environment with vRA Cloud templates: through a vRA template or through a network profile.
Demo Product Versions  vRA Cloud VMC on AWS (SDDC version 1.13)  Prerequisites VMC on AWS:
 Active SDDC  vRA Cloud:
 Basic infrastructure configured for the VMC on AWS environment (Cloud Proxy, Cloud Account, Project, Cloud Zone, Flavor Mapping, Image Mapping)  Methods  Using vRA template Using vRA network profile  Demos / Examples Method 1: Using vRA Template  In a vRA Cloud template in vRA Cloud Assembly, drag a Cloud Agnostic Security Group resource on the canvas and connect it to the machine you&rsquo;d like to place in the security group.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Using Existing NSX-T Security Groups in VMC on AWS with vRA Cloud</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/es/2021-03-22-vrac-vmc-nsxt-existing-security-groups.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 05:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Autor</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/es/2021-03-22-vrac-vmc-nsxt-existing-security-groups.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[~ Este post será traducido al español próximamente ~ There are different ways you can consume existing NSX-T security groups in a VMC on AWS environment with vRA Cloud templates: through a vRA template or through a network profile.
Demo Product Versions  vRA Cloud VMC on AWS (SDDC version 1.13)  Prerequisites VMC on AWS:
 Active SDDC  vRA Cloud:
 Basic infrastructure configured for the VMC on AWS environment (Cloud Proxy, Cloud Account, Project, Cloud Zone, Flavor Mapping, Image Mapping)  Methods  Using vRA template Using vRA network profile  Demos / Examples Method 1: Using vRA Template  Under &ldquo;Compute Groups&rdquo; in the VMC on AWS UI, create a security group.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Part 8: Create a vRA 8 (Cloud) Blueprint with On-demand NSX-T One-Arm Load Balancer</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/es/2020-07-22-vracloud-nsxt-on-demand-one-arm-load-balancer.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 07:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Autor</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/es/2020-07-22-vracloud-nsxt-on-demand-one-arm-load-balancer.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[~ Este post será traducido al español próximamente ~ You can create a vRA Cloud blueprint to deploy machines and place them behind an on-demand NSX-T one-arm load balancer. This method creates a tier-1 router then configures load balancing services, adding virtual server, server pool, and application profile (monitor too if you want). This method should work in vRA 8.1, but I used vRA Cloud to create the demo.
Below is a simplified diagram of a NSX-T one-arm load balancer.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Parte 7 de la Serie Blog vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T: Plantilla con &#39;One-Arm Load Balaner&#39; (equilibrador de carge) Existente de NSX-T</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/es/2020-07-20-vracloud-nsxt-existing-one-arm-load-balancer.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 07:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Autor</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/es/2020-07-20-vracloud-nsxt-existing-one-arm-load-balancer.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Puede crear una plantilla vRA Cloud para desplegar máquinas y ponerlas detrás de en un &ldquo;one-arm load balancer&rdquo; existente de NSX-T. Este proceso no crea los enrutadors lógicos bajo demanda. El proceso usa un &ldquo;one-arm load balancer&rdquo; existente y simplemente agregar &ldquo;virtual server&rdquo; (servidor virtual), &ldquo;server pool&rdquo; (grupo de servidores), y &ldquo;application profile&rdquo; (perfil de aplicación). Puede crear un &ldquo;monitor&rdquo; (monitor de máquina virtual) también si quiere. Este proceso funciona con vRA 8.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Considerations When Using Layer 2 Bridges for NSX-V to NSX-T Migration</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/es/2020-04-17-using-l2-bridges-v2t-migration.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 04:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Autor</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/es/2020-04-17-using-l2-bridges-v2t-migration.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[~ Este post será traducido al español próximamente ~ I recently had a customer who asked for some general feedback on their high-level plan to migrate from NSX-V to NSX-T using layer 2 bridges. Although every environment is different and the details of migration procedures should be tailored to each environment, I thought I&rsquo;d share the general guidance I gave to this customer in case there are some points here that may be transferrable to other similar NSX-V to NSX-T migration plans.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Parte 6 de la Serie Blog vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T: Plantilla vRA 8 con Grupos de Seguridad Bajo Demanda</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/es/2020-03-23-vra8-nsxt-on-demand-security-group.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 04:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Autor</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/es/2020-03-23-vra8-nsxt-on-demand-security-group.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Puede crear una plantilla vRA 8 para desplegar máquinas y ponerlas en un grupo de seguridad bajo demanda.
Versiones de Productos Demostración (Demo)  vSphere 6.5 U3 vRA 8.0.1 (incluyendo vRSLCM y vIDM) NSX-T 2.5.1 vSAN 6.6.1  Prerrequisitos vRA 8:
 Cuenta conectada de NSX-T Infraestructura básica configurada (proyectos, zonas de nube, &ldquo;image mappings&rdquo; o asignaciones de imagen, &ldquo;flavor mappings&rdquo; o asignaciones de tipo)  NSX-T:
 red configurado  Información General de Proceso  Cree o revise un perfil de red.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Parte 5 de la Serie Blog vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T: Plantilla vRA 8 con Grupos de Seguridad Existentes (etiqueta de puerto de segmento)</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/es/2020-03-20-vra8-nsxt-existing-security-group-using-segment-port-tags.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 05:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Autor</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/es/2020-03-20-vra8-nsxt-existing-security-group-using-segment-port-tags.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Puede crear una plantilla vRA 8 para desplegar máquinas y ponerlas en un grupo de seguridad existente de NSX-T usando etiquetas de puerto de segmento de NSX-T.
Update: July 26, 2021 No puede usar etiquetas de puerto de segmento de NSX-T empezando con vRA 8.2. Gracias a mi colega Mukesh Idnani para este descubrimiento!
Versiones de Productos Demostración (Demo)  vSphere 6.5 U3 vRA 8.0.1 (incluyendo vRSLCM y vIDM) NSX-T 2.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Parte 4 de la Serie Blog vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T: Plantilla vRA 8 con Grupos de Seguridad Existentes (etiqueta vRA)</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/es/2020-03-19-vra8-nsxt-existing-security-group-using-vra-tags.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 07:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Autor</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/es/2020-03-19-vra8-nsxt-existing-security-group-using-vra-tags.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Puede crear una plantilla vRA 8 para desplegar máquinas y ponerlas en un grupo de seguridad existente de NSX-T usando etiquetas vRA.
Versiones de Productos Demostración (Demo)  vSphere 6.5 U3 vRA 8.0.1 (incluyendo vRSLCM y vIDM) NSX-T 2.5.1 vSAN 6.6.1  Prerrequisitos vRA 8:
 Cuenta conectada de NSX-T Infraestructura básica configurada (Proyectos, Zonas de nube, Asignaciones de imagen, Asignaciones de tipo)  NSX-T:
 Grupos de seguridad configurados  Información General de Proceso  Cree una etiqueta en el grupo de seguridad existente.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
