<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>vRA - Category - 288clouds</title>
        <link>https://288clouds.com/categories/vra.html</link>
        <description>vRA - Category - 288clouds</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 07:53:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://288clouds.com/categories/vra.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Create a vRA Cloud Blueprint with On-demand NSX-T One-Arm Load Balancer</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-07-22-vracloud-nsxt-on-demand-one-arm-load-balancer.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 07:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-07-22-vracloud-nsxt-on-demand-one-arm-load-balancer.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create a vRA Cloud blueprint to deploy machines and place them behind an on-demand NSX-T one-arm load balancer. This method creates a tier-1 router then configures load balancing services, adding virtual server, server pool, and application profile (monitor too if you want). This method should work in vRA 8.1, but I used vRA Cloud to create the demo.
Below is a simplified diagram of a NSX-T one-arm load balancer.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Create a vRA Cloud Blueprint with Existing NSX-T One-Arm Load Balancer</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-07-20-vracloud-nsxt-existing-one-arm-load-balancer.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 07:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-07-20-vracloud-nsxt-existing-one-arm-load-balancer.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create a vRA Cloud blueprint to deploy machines and place them behind an existing NSX-T one-arm load balancer. This method does not create any on-demand tier-1 routers. It uses the existing load balancer and simply adds virtual server, server pool, and application profile (monitor too if you want). This method should work in vRA 8.1 as well, but I used vRA Cloud to create the demo.
Below is a simplified diagram of a NSX-T one-arm load balancer.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Part 6: vRA 8 Blueprint with On-demand Security Group</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-23-vra8-nsxt-on-demand-security-group.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 04:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-23-vra8-nsxt-on-demand-security-group.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create a vRA 8 blueprint to deploy machines and place them in an on-demand NSX-T security group.
Demo Product Versions  vSphere 6.5 U3 vRA 8.0.1 (including vRSLCM and vIDM) NSX-T 2.5.1 vSAN 6.6.1  Prerequisites vRA 8:
 NSX-T account connected Basic infrastructure configured (Projects, Cloud Zones, Flavor Mappings, Image Mappings)  NSX-T:
 logical network(s) configured  Process Overview  Create or edit a network profile. Select which existing security groups you&rsquo;d like to use.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Part 5: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing Security Group (segment port tag)</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-20-vra8-nsxt-existing-security-group-using-segment-port-tags.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 05:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-20-vra8-nsxt-existing-security-group-using-segment-port-tags.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create a vRA 8 blueprint to deploy machines and place them in existing NSX-T security group(s) by putting tags on the machine segment port(s).
Demo Product Versions  vSphere 6.5 U3 vRA 8.0.1 (including vRSLCM and vIDM) NSX-T 2.5.1 vSAN 6.6.1  Prerequisites vRA 8:
 NSX-T account connected Basic infrastructure configured (Projects, Cloud Zones, Flavor Mappings, Image Mappings)  NSX-T:
 Security group(s) configured  Process Overview  Configure Membership Criteria of the existing security group(s).]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Part 4: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing Security Group (vRA tag)</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-19-vra8-nsxt-existing-security-group-using-vra-tags.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 07:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-19-vra8-nsxt-existing-security-group-using-vra-tags.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create a vRA 8 blueprint to deploy machines and place them in existing NSX-T security group(s) using vRA tags.
Demo Product Versions  vSphere 6.5 U3 vRA 8.0.1 (including vRSLCM and vIDM) NSX-T 2.5.1 vSAN 6.6.1  Prerequisites vRA 8:
 NSX-T account connected Basic infrastructure configured (Projects, Cloud Zones, Flavor Mappings, Image Mappings)  NSX-T:
 security group(s) configured  Process Overview  Create a tag on the existing security group(s).]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Part 3: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing Security Group (network profile)</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-18-vra8-nsxt-existing-security-group-using-network-profile.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 06:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-18-vra8-nsxt-existing-security-group-using-network-profile.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create a vRA 8 blueprint to deploy machines and place them in existing NSX-T security group(s) using a network profile.
Note that with this method, however, any and all security groups that you select in the network profile will be applied to the machines. If you have multiple machines in a blueprint and want to specify which security group each machine should use then use vRA tag or segment port tag (refer to series part 4 &amp; 5 for those methods).]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Customize Machine and On-demand Network Names</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-17-customize-machine-on-demand-network-names.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-17-customize-machine-on-demand-network-names.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[vRA 8 blueprint gives random names and numbers to the VMs and on-demand NSX-T networks deployed if you do not specify a naming convention. This blog will cover how you can customize the names of your VMs and on-demand NSX-T networks when they are deployed from a vRA 8 blueprint.
Demo Product Versions  vSphere 6.5 U3 vRA 8.0.1 (including vRSLCM and vIDM) NSX-T 2.5.1 vSAN 6.6.1  Prerequisites vRA 8:]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Part 2: vRA 8 Blueprint with On-demand Routed NSX-T Networks</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-16-vra8-blueprint-nsxt-on-demand-routed-network.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 07:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-16-vra8-blueprint-nsxt-on-demand-routed-network.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create a vRA 8 blueprint to create an on-demand routed NSX-T network and deploy machines connected to these newly created network. When you tell the blueprint to create an on-demand routed NSX-T network, vRA 8 actually creates a tier-1 gateway that connects to the pre-existing tier-0 gateway. It then creates an on-demand network and attaches it to the tier-1 gateway that it has created.
Demo Product Versions  vSphere 6.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Part 1: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing NSX-T Networks</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-13-vra8-blueprint-nsxt-existing-network.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 07:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-13-vra8-blueprint-nsxt-existing-network.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create a vRA 8 blueprint to deploy machines on existing NSX-T networks.
Demo Product Versions  vSphere 6.5 U3 vRA 8.0.1 (including vRSLCM and vIDM) NSX-T 2.5.1 vSAN 6.6.1  Prerequisites vRA 8:
 NSX-T account connected Basic infrastructure configured (Projects, Cloud Zones, Flavor Mappings, Image Mappings)  NSX-T:
 logical router (tier-0 or tier-1) configured logical segment(s) attached to a logical router  Process Overview  Set up the existing networks with IP ranges you want to use for the machines.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Overview</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-12-vra8-nsxt-blog-series-overview.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 09:44:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-12-vra8-nsxt-blog-series-overview.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[With the recent release of vRA 8.0, I have been receiving many questions from customers about how vRA 8 can leverage NSX-T.
This blog series will focus on demonstrating how you can create vRA 8 blueprints that utilize NSX-T constructs.
Here is a list of blogs that I am planning on creating for this series (as of March 15, 2020):
 Part 1: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing NSX-T Networks Part 2: vRA 8 Blueprint with On-demand Routed NSX-T Networks Part 3: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing Security Groups (network profile) Part 4: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing Security Groups (vRA tag) Part 5: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing Security Groups (segment port tag) Part 6: vRA 8 Blueprint with On-demand Security Groups Part 7: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing NSX-T One-Arm Load Balancer Part 8: vRA 8 Blueprint with On-demand NSX-T One-Arm Load Balancer Part 9: vRA 8 Blueprint with On-demand NAT NSX-T Networks  Note: the list of blogs is subject to change.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
