<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>NSX - Tag - 288clouds</title>
        <link>https://288clouds.com/tags/nsx.html</link>
        <description>NSX - Tag - 288clouds</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 05:52:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://288clouds.com/tags/nsx.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>On-demand NSX-T Networks with vRA Cloud in VMC on AWS VS. On-Prem vSphere</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-30-vrac-nsxt-on-demand-networks-vmc-on-prem-differences.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 05:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-30-vrac-nsxt-on-demand-networks-vmc-on-prem-differences.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create on-demand NSX-T networks using a vRA Cloud template in a VMC on AWS environment as well as in an on-prem vSphere environment. However, there are some differences between how on-demand NSX-T networks are created in these two environments due to limitations with vRA at the time of writing this post.
On-demand Network Types vRA Cloud Assembly has several on-demand network types available depending on the resource you choose.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Creating On-demand Distributed Firewall Rules in VMC on AWS with vRA Cloud</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-29-vrac-vmc-nsxt-on-demand-dfw.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 05:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-29-vrac-vmc-nsxt-on-demand-dfw.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Let&rsquo;s explore how you can create on-demand distributed firewall rules in a VMC on AWS environment with a vRA Cloud template.
Demo Product Versions vRA Cloud VMC on AWS (SDDC version 1.13) Prerequisites VMC on AWS:
Active SDDC vRA Cloud:
Basic infrastructure configured for the VMC on AWS environment (Cloud Proxy, Cloud Account, Project, Cloud Zone, Flavor Mapping, Image Mapping) Process Overview Create a template that adds a new security group to the deployment.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Using On-demand NSX-T Security Groups in VMC on AWS with vRA Cloud</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-23-vrac-vmc-nsxt-on-demand-security-groups.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 05:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-23-vrac-vmc-nsxt-on-demand-security-groups.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[There are different ways you can create on-demand NSX-T security groups in a VMC on AWS environment with vRA Cloud templates: through a vRA template or through a network profile.
Demo Product Versions vRA Cloud VMC on AWS (SDDC version 1.13) Prerequisites VMC on AWS:
Active SDDC vRA Cloud:
Basic infrastructure configured for the VMC on AWS environment (Cloud Proxy, Cloud Account, Project, Cloud Zone, Flavor Mapping, Image Mapping) Methods Using vRA template Using vRA network profile Demos / Examples Method 1: Using vRA Template In a vRA Cloud template in vRA Cloud Assembly, drag a Cloud Agnostic Security Group resource on the canvas and connect it to the machine you&rsquo;d like to place in the security group.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Using Existing NSX-T Security Groups in VMC on AWS with vRA Cloud</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-22-vrac-vmc-nsxt-existing-security-groups.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 05:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-22-vrac-vmc-nsxt-existing-security-groups.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[There are different ways you can consume existing NSX-T security groups in a VMC on AWS environment with vRA Cloud templates: through a vRA template or through a network profile.
Demo Product Versions vRA Cloud VMC on AWS (SDDC version 1.13) Prerequisites VMC on AWS:
Active SDDC vRA Cloud:
Basic infrastructure configured for the VMC on AWS environment (Cloud Proxy, Cloud Account, Project, Cloud Zone, Flavor Mapping, Image Mapping) Methods Using vRA template Using vRA network profile Demos / Examples Method 1: Using vRA Template Under &ldquo;Compute Groups&rdquo; in the VMC on AWS UI, create a security group.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Common Questions around VCDX-NV</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-09-23-vcdx-nv-common-questions.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 07:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-09-23-vcdx-nv-common-questions.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[When I was starting my journey to achieve the VCDX-NV certification, I had a lot of questions. Now after going through the certification process, I thought it might be useful if I help answer some of those questions in a blogpost. Here we go!
Common FAQs Should I use NSX-V or NSX-T in my design? This is entirely up to you. Of course you have to be technical and extremely knowledgeable with the product (NSX-V or NSX-T), but remember that VCDX is an exam for architects.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
