<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>vRA Cloud - Tag - 288clouds</title>
        <link>https://288clouds.com/tags/vra-cloud.html</link>
        <description>vRA Cloud - Tag - 288clouds</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 07:53:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://288clouds.com/tags/vra-cloud.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>VCP-CMA 2020 (2V0-31.20) Exam Study Guide - Sections 1-3</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-12-13-vcp-cma-2020-section-1.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 07:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-12-13-vcp-cma-2020-section-1.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[This study guide aligns with the exam blueprint for the Professional VMware vRealize Automation 8.1 exam (2V0-31.20), which leads to the VMware Certified Professional - Cloud Management and Automation 2020 certification. The exam is 135 minutes with 70 questions.
This study guide has been created to help myself study for the exam, but I hope you find this helpful in your own preparation for the exam. If you want official training to prepare for the exam, please refer to VMware Learning.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Part 8: Create a vRA 8 (Cloud) Blueprint with On-demand NSX-T One-Arm Load Balancer</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-07-22-vracloud-nsxt-on-demand-one-arm-load-balancer.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 07:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-07-22-vracloud-nsxt-on-demand-one-arm-load-balancer.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create a vRA Cloud blueprint to deploy machines and place them behind an on-demand NSX-T one-arm load balancer. This method creates a tier-1 router then configures load balancing services, adding virtual server, server pool, and application profile (monitor too if you want). This method should work in vRA 8.1, but I used vRA Cloud to create the demo.
Below is a simplified diagram of a NSX-T one-arm load balancer.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Part 7: Create a vRA 8 (Cloud) Blueprint with Existing NSX-T One-Arm Load Balancer</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-07-20-vracloud-nsxt-existing-one-arm-load-balancer.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 07:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-07-20-vracloud-nsxt-existing-one-arm-load-balancer.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create a vRA Cloud blueprint to deploy machines and place them behind an existing NSX-T one-arm load balancer. This method does not create any on-demand tier-1 routers. It uses the existing load balancer and simply adds virtual server, server pool, and application profile (monitor too if you want). This method should work in vRA 8.1 as well, but I used vRA Cloud to create the demo.
Below is a simplified diagram of a NSX-T one-arm load balancer.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Overview</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-12-vra8-nsxt-blog-series-overview.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 09:44:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-12-vra8-nsxt-blog-series-overview.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[With the recent release of vRA 8.0, I have been receiving many questions from customers about how vRA 8 can leverage NSX-T.
This blog series will focus on demonstrating how you can create vRA 8 blueprints that utilize NSX-T constructs.
Here is a list of blogs that I am planning on creating for this series (as of March 15, 2020):
 Part 1: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing NSX-T Networks Part 2: vRA 8 Blueprint with On-demand Routed NSX-T Networks Part 3: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing Security Groups (network profile) Part 4: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing Security Groups (vRA tag) Part 5: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing Security Groups (segment port tag) Part 6: vRA 8 Blueprint with On-demand Security Groups Part 7: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing NSX-T One-Arm Load Balancer Part 8: vRA 8 Blueprint with On-demand NSX-T One-Arm Load Balancer Part 9: vRA 8 Blueprint with On-demand NAT NSX-T Networks  Note: the list of blogs is subject to change.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
