<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>NSX-T - Tag - 288clouds</title>
        <link>https://288clouds.com/tags/nsx-t.html</link>
        <description>NSX-T - Tag - 288clouds</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 05:52:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://288clouds.com/tags/nsx-t.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>On-demand NSX-T Networks with vRA Cloud in VMC on AWS VS. On-Prem vSphere</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-30-vrac-nsxt-on-demand-networks-vmc-on-prem-differences.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 05:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-30-vrac-nsxt-on-demand-networks-vmc-on-prem-differences.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create on-demand NSX-T networks using a vRA Cloud template in a VMC on AWS environment as well as in an on-prem vSphere environment. However, there are some differences between how on-demand NSX-T networks are created in these two environments due to limitations with vRA at the time of writing this post.
On-demand Network Types vRA Cloud Assembly has several on-demand network types available depending on the resource you choose.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Creating On-demand Distributed Firewall Rules in VMC on AWS with vRA Cloud</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-29-vrac-vmc-nsxt-on-demand-dfw.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 05:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-29-vrac-vmc-nsxt-on-demand-dfw.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Let&rsquo;s explore how you can create on-demand distributed firewall rules in a VMC on AWS environment with a vRA Cloud template.
Demo Product Versions  vRA Cloud VMC on AWS (SDDC version 1.13)  Prerequisites VMC on AWS:
 Active SDDC  vRA Cloud:
 Basic infrastructure configured for the VMC on AWS environment (Cloud Proxy, Cloud Account, Project, Cloud Zone, Flavor Mapping, Image Mapping)  Process Overview  Create a template that adds a new security group to the deployment.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Using On-demand NSX-T Security Groups in VMC on AWS with vRA Cloud</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-23-vrac-vmc-nsxt-on-demand-security-groups.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 05:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-23-vrac-vmc-nsxt-on-demand-security-groups.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[There are different ways you can create on-demand NSX-T security groups in a VMC on AWS environment with vRA Cloud templates: through a vRA template or through a network profile.
Demo Product Versions  vRA Cloud VMC on AWS (SDDC version 1.13)  Prerequisites VMC on AWS:
 Active SDDC  vRA Cloud:
 Basic infrastructure configured for the VMC on AWS environment (Cloud Proxy, Cloud Account, Project, Cloud Zone, Flavor Mapping, Image Mapping)  Methods  Using vRA template Using vRA network profile  Demos / Examples Method 1: Using vRA Template  In a vRA Cloud template in vRA Cloud Assembly, drag a Cloud Agnostic Security Group resource on the canvas and connect it to the machine you&rsquo;d like to place in the security group.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Using Existing NSX-T Security Groups in VMC on AWS with vRA Cloud</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-22-vrac-vmc-nsxt-existing-security-groups.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 05:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2021-03-22-vrac-vmc-nsxt-existing-security-groups.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[There are different ways you can consume existing NSX-T security groups in a VMC on AWS environment with vRA Cloud templates: through a vRA template or through a network profile.
Demo Product Versions  vRA Cloud VMC on AWS (SDDC version 1.13)  Prerequisites VMC on AWS:
 Active SDDC  vRA Cloud:
 Basic infrastructure configured for the VMC on AWS environment (Cloud Proxy, Cloud Account, Project, Cloud Zone, Flavor Mapping, Image Mapping)  Methods  Using vRA template Using vRA network profile  Demos / Examples Method 1: Using vRA Template  Under &ldquo;Compute Groups&rdquo; in the VMC on AWS UI, create a security group.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Part 8: Create a vRA 8 (Cloud) Blueprint with On-demand NSX-T One-Arm Load Balancer</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-07-22-vracloud-nsxt-on-demand-one-arm-load-balancer.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 07:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-07-22-vracloud-nsxt-on-demand-one-arm-load-balancer.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create a vRA Cloud blueprint to deploy machines and place them behind an on-demand NSX-T one-arm load balancer. This method creates a tier-1 router then configures load balancing services, adding virtual server, server pool, and application profile (monitor too if you want). This method should work in vRA 8.1, but I used vRA Cloud to create the demo.
Below is a simplified diagram of a NSX-T one-arm load balancer.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Part 7: Create a vRA 8 (Cloud) Blueprint with Existing NSX-T One-Arm Load Balancer</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-07-20-vracloud-nsxt-existing-one-arm-load-balancer.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 07:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-07-20-vracloud-nsxt-existing-one-arm-load-balancer.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create a vRA Cloud blueprint to deploy machines and place them behind an existing NSX-T one-arm load balancer. This method does not create any on-demand tier-1 routers. It uses the existing load balancer and simply adds virtual server, server pool, and application profile (monitor too if you want). This method should work in vRA 8.1 as well, but I used vRA Cloud to create the demo.
Below is a simplified diagram of a NSX-T one-arm load balancer.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Considerations When Using Layer 2 Bridges for NSX-V to NSX-T Migration</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-04-17-using-l2-bridges-v2t-migration.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 04:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-04-17-using-l2-bridges-v2t-migration.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I recently had a customer who asked for some general feedback on their high-level plan to migrate from NSX-V to NSX-T using layer 2 bridges. Although every environment is different and the details of migration procedures should be tailored to each environment, I thought I&rsquo;d share the general guidance I gave to this customer in case there are some points here that may be transferrable to other similar NSX-V to NSX-T migration plans.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Part 6: vRA 8 Blueprint with On-demand Security Group</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-23-vra8-nsxt-on-demand-security-group.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 04:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-23-vra8-nsxt-on-demand-security-group.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create a vRA 8 blueprint to deploy machines and place them in an on-demand NSX-T security group.
Demo Product Versions  vSphere 6.5 U3 vRA 8.0.1 (including vRSLCM and vIDM) NSX-T 2.5.1 vSAN 6.6.1  Prerequisites vRA 8:
 NSX-T account connected Basic infrastructure configured (Projects, Cloud Zones, Flavor Mappings, Image Mappings)  NSX-T:
 logical network(s) configured  Process Overview  Create or edit a network profile. Select which existing security groups you&rsquo;d like to use.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Part 5: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing Security Group (segment port tag)</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-20-vra8-nsxt-existing-security-group-using-segment-port-tags.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 05:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-20-vra8-nsxt-existing-security-group-using-segment-port-tags.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create a vRA 8 blueprint to deploy machines and place them in existing NSX-T security group(s) by putting tags on the machine segment port(s).
Demo Product Versions  vSphere 6.5 U3 vRA 8.0.1 (including vRSLCM and vIDM) NSX-T 2.5.1 vSAN 6.6.1  Prerequisites vRA 8:
 NSX-T account connected Basic infrastructure configured (Projects, Cloud Zones, Flavor Mappings, Image Mappings)  NSX-T:
 Security group(s) configured  Process Overview  Configure Membership Criteria of the existing security group(s).]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>vRA 8 &#43; NSX-T Blog Series Part 4: vRA 8 Blueprint with Existing Security Group (vRA tag)</title>
    <link>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-19-vra8-nsxt-existing-security-group-using-vra-tags.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 07:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://288clouds.com/2020-03-19-vra8-nsxt-existing-security-group-using-vra-tags.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[You can create a vRA 8 blueprint to deploy machines and place them in existing NSX-T security group(s) using vRA tags.
Demo Product Versions  vSphere 6.5 U3 vRA 8.0.1 (including vRSLCM and vIDM) NSX-T 2.5.1 vSAN 6.6.1  Prerequisites vRA 8:
 NSX-T account connected Basic infrastructure configured (Projects, Cloud Zones, Flavor Mappings, Image Mappings)  NSX-T:
 security group(s) configured  Process Overview  Create a tag on the existing security group(s).]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
